I'm going to go buy some merchandise.
Let's go. Let's go.
I like where you're coming from.
Wow. Can I buy some stuff?
Sure.
Oh, man, that line is crazy.
It's so thick.
Come on!
Ha!
You scared me.
Thank you very much. I'm so surprised.
Hello everyone. I'm Mikuni Takahashi from Hinatosaka Holotisyx.
I'm Nao Takahashi.
Do you know what we have in common?
Do you know?
If you want, this is enough to make us friends.
Yes, that's right.
The correct answer is that we like anime.
Today, we went to Anime Italy!
We did it!
Wow, it's huge!
I'm going to buy a lot of goods today!
I'm so happy!
I'll be on the Nakasaka channel on the first day of the show!
First time!
And this selfie!
There he is!
Is he an animated character?
Anime contingent.
Store manager Store manager
Store manager
Oh, my God.
They're here.
Three Shops.
Thank you for your help.
Thank you.
Cool.
I'm going to get some stuff.
Oh, my God.
Here we are at the book corner on the second floor.
Amazing.
On a personal note, the day of this photo shoot was my birthday!
My 20th birthday.
That's right.
I'm thinking of having a manga adult party for the first time in my life, so
I'm going to ask some of my senior comic book friends to come along.
I know a lot of them, like this one that's in the picture right now.
Let's find the manga we're looking for.
What is Yukari's target manga?
I wonder if there are any... I wonder if there are all the volumes.
Oh, no, all the volumes of haiku!
We both love haiku.
Oh, I wonder if we have it.
Got it?
Yes!
I love Tokyo Goal.
I've been watching the anime for weeks now.
I thought if I love it so much, I'd like to get the manga too.
I'll buy it! I'll buy it!
Letter today
I'm nervous.
Wow!
First of all, this way.
Oh, my God.
Let's put it in, let's put it in, let's put it in.
There's no 7s and 8s.
There's no Earth.
Let's just do it.
That's great.
I'll buy it.
It's heavy.
Heavy?
I'm so happy with the weight.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to buy it!
Next is the anime goods area.
Let's get down to business!
Here we are at the Diet!
Here we are!
Wow, right in front of us is our favorite
I'd like to take a look at some of the background goods.
I'd like to take a look.
Let's take a look.
Oh, no!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.Wait.
Who is your favorite character?
Something they teach at every high school.
Yes, yes, yes.
I can do it, but my favorite is...
I like Suga the crow.
We talked about that.
Mr. Suga is my favorite.
I like Mr. Noyaku.
Mr. Wild Pill.
He's cool.
He's cool, isn't he?
I'm going to see a lot of Arka.
This one too.
There's an Akusta!
It's the same title as the one in the background.
No kidding?
But I like Kenmon too.
I like Aku-Ashi, too.
What should I do with Random?
I don't know.
I want to do something random.
My camera can afford it.
I didn't do it yesterday.
I'm worried about it.
I can't seem to get any random guesses.
It's my birthday today.
I might get it. I might get it.
One of these is not enough.
I always buy two or three.
I buy two.
I'll pick one.
The one that freaked me out.
I'll pick this one and this one.
You're picking too fast.
This one.
Let's see what we get.
Enjoy opening it.
hirowaka ya
There's a Hirowaka!
Oh, no.
The Hirowaka...
hirowaka is...
Who do you like?
Eh, Todoroki.
Together
Tororoki and I like Tsuyu-chan.
I like Tsuyu-chan
There's so much randomness.
I don't really have a random.
I want to do random.
But there's too many.
I don't know about this.
This one's cute.
I'll give you this one.
I'll just go with one.
I'm going to go with this one.I'm doing this.
Okay, I'm going to B.
Come on, let's push off.
I'm going.
Yay.
Round ten.
Round 10.
I like the field.
A field?
I like strong female characters.
I like...
I like spikes.
They look like this.
It's random, right?
You know...
Not at all.
Random is super inorganic.
Can I buy an Axter with spikes?
Can I buy some?
It's cute.
I just wanted to get one.
It's okay.
I can't find Mr. Nohara.
I don't see Mr. Nohara.
Maybe I'll just do a random one.
A dozen.
This one is absolutely adorable.
I'll pick one.
I guess we're going for the field.So you're aiming for the field.
I like togis, too.
Then let's get this one.
I'll get this one.
I'll buy what you like from here.
We're running out of time.
I'm going.
I'll see you later.
This is my favorite bride from Gombun!
I often talk with Haruyo Yamaguchi, one of our members.
Haruyo is Itsuki's favorite character.
I like Miku.
We come from the same place.
There you are.
It's Miku.
We met.
I'm also interested in Motohana.
Miku's my favorite.
I think I'll go to this one at random.
It's funny how they keep coming back to the same place.
I think they said they were going to break up.
I'm thinking of doing a random one too.
There are only four of them.
I think I'll get two.
I'll take this one.
I'll get this one.
I want Miku to appear.
I'll go to the magnet shop.
Let's go to Raschichi. Let's go to Las Vegas.
Well, I went back.
I'm going to buy a clear file.
I really want this drawstring!
There it is.
What a surprise!
I ran into him!
There's Ricco here!
I found it... just now.
Where is it?
Here!
I love Licorice... and I love Licorice... and I love Licorice...
Licorice!
We're Takina and Licorice, right?
I'm a Takina girl.
I like Takina!
I like you.
Hey...
Look.
This one's a huwanuizu.
This is super cute.
I want a cafe Takina.
This one.
Excuse me from the back.
This is super cool.
What's that?
It's an eye-catcher.
What's an eye-catcher?
After the commercials are over, before the show starts.After the commercials are over, before the main program starts.
There's a moment of silence.
That's the eye-catcher.
It's got all those C's in it.
A and B.
That's what this is?
C.
This one.
Can I get three?
Sure.
How many are there?
There were only a few left.
I don't think we'll run into each other.
I'll buy them.
I think I've already changed my belt.
I'll go check out.
I'll go pay the bill.
Please do.
Welcome.
I'm so scared.
If you're short, there's always someone to help you.
No, no, no, no, you've got senpai.
Great, great, great price.
Oh, I'm scared.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay. Oh, no!
Thank God it's just the three of us.
Okay, I'll write Haginao.
Please, two for me.
I like Random.
Random... you're right, I buy a lot of Random. Random, sure, I've been buying a lot of stuff.
But you know what? I didn't buy enough.
I really wanted to see more.
I wish I had more time.
If I came here in private, I'd probably be here for another three hours.
Real time.
Well, don't think that's all of it.
I didn't think you were going to be there much, but you were.
You're right.
I went on a shopping spree.
I'm here.
Wow, this blue dress is my idea of happiness.
I feel so animated!
Now let's develop it!
All right!
First of all
This way
This way...
I bought my favorite Tokyo Guru!
Volumes 1 to 14.
I wanted to taste the difference between the anime and the manga.
So I bought them because I wanted to taste them too!
And here's the next item!
Next goods
Then, I want to take them all out once.
Wow!
Wow.
First one.First one
Hi-Q hand towel
This is a normal banner of Aoba Josai High School.
I wonder if it is called a banner.
Hand Towel and Pose Towel of
How nice!
I bought it!
I thought I'd use it for something serious.
I got a super order!
I love the colors!
I love the messiness of it.
Okay, next.
I bought this clear file from Love Live, which I was super into when I was in elementary school.
There's my favorite character, Yo Watanabe.
Super cute!
I love it!
I bought it!
Next!
Love Live!
First of all, here it is!
This is an acrylic stand of Rin Hoshizora.
I want to show everyone how cute she is!
It's a big collection of my favorite members!
It's a big grouping of my favorite members!
From Love Live Muse
Minami Kotori
Rin Hoshizora
And from Love Live Sunshine Aqua
Watanabe Hiroshi!
I bought all my favorite members! I bought all my favorite members.
I will give them back to you at home.
I'm so happy!
The acrylic stands.
Yes.
It's nice.
And...
Love Live is still here.
This is Love Live, too.
I bought a random one.
Who did you buy this for?
It's Aqua.
I'm going for Hiroshi Watanabe.
There are 9 members.
There are only nine.
What do you think?
I'll go.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Come on!
Not yet.
I'm sorry.
You know what I mean.
I've seen it before.
I don't see it.
Here we go.
Ready?
clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap!
(clap) clap!Hey!
Riko?
This is Riko Sakurauchi.
She's cute.
I could've bought a few more of these.
There's this one, too.
There's randomness!
That's all for Love Live!
Thank you very much.
Next is an anime called "Licorice Recoil".
We both love it.
We both like the character Takina.
I got an acrylic stand this time!
So cute!
It will enrich our house!
I'm going to display it!
That's it for my personal items!
I am satisfied.
Now let's go to Naosa.
Oh! There are so many!
So much randomness!
There's a lot of randomness.
Okay, first of all...
Hi-Q hand towels!
Where shall we go with this?
This is a bag of ticks.
Even if you buy a bag tick
I wanted to buy a Calson, but we didn't have a Calson.
This time...
I'm also interested in bagged ticks.Bag ticks are also my favorite.
I bought a bag of ticks.
And after Mikuni and I saw this, it fell apart, so I bought one more.
I had it in my hand once, like, "I'm going to use this drawstring...
I had to have it, so I bought this one. It's a drawstring for Crow High School.
I take it with me when I go to TV or when I go to my dressing room.
I get excited when I have goods that I like.
I'm done with the backgrounds for now.
I bought an acrylic stand of spikes.
When I saw it, I thought I had to buy it.
I know, I know.
I picked it up right away.
The rest is the same at random.
Trading backgrounds, the Medikal acrylic key folder collection.
I'll go ahead and say that my favorite characters are Yasu-san and Koigawa-san from Aya-Uku, Nishino.
I like Suga-san and Akasoku.
I'll open the first one.
I can't tell by the way their hands feel, so I guess they're the same shape.
I've never seen anything like this. Ready?
Who's that? Sunshine.
Mr. Daichi? Mr. Daichi. Mr. Daichi, the Crow Prime Minister.
It's got his lines written all over it.
This one's extra special for me.
We're not here to protect our friends. We're all here to take the sky.
Very cool, Mr. Daichi!
I get Hyuga in the background at random a lot.
That's because we're on the same side.
That's why? There's so many Hyuga's in the background.
Do you think she'll show up? Ready?
What? What?
What?
I got black.
Cat's-Eye Black.
Black.
Oh, no.
I knew you had it.
This can't be right.
I'm at a serious disadvantage.
I've got a lot of odds stacked against me.
I should've bought some more of this.
Next time...
I'm not going to do the whole flower thing first.
Okay, I'll take one.
I have two.
No, it's a frame magnet.
There was only one left.
I got it on the last one.
I'm going for...
Miku!
It's the last one.
But it's only one-fifth of the total.
Miku-chan, Miku-chan, Miku-chan
In love...
Aaaaah!
Here it is! It's the first time! Such a scene! I'm so happy!
Look at this! It's so cute!
Thank you so much!
No, this is a good one! No, you got a good one out of this one!
Good, good, good!
Please go for it!
I'm a trading pet acrylic mascot!
Mascot?
I'm looking at it!
Coins! What? Itsuki? It's Itsuki!
A rabbit!
Itsuki is Haruyo Yamaguchi's favorite character!
I like Itsuki too, so I'm happy!
Next up, the acrylic petit stand from the Genius Round!
I like Nohara Kurosaki, by the way!
Se-no, Jan! Panda!
And he was a brave panda!
I think I like that senior panda a lot.
Thank you.
Welcome to WAKAYA.
I was a panda.
Acrylic key chains, 7 kinds in total.
I want to get this one.
Here we go.
Oh, no...
I got a field!
He's so cute!
It's amazing!
I have a present for you. - Really?
Yes, you can have it.
It's my birthday. Happy birthday.
So, if you like anime, you can do an exchange or something like that. If you like anime, you can do things like exchanges and arity.
I'm sure you'll enjoy it too!
Next is my Hero Academia acrylic stand!
I'm version B and I'm version A.
I'm going for Chi-chan I'm going for Todoroki
I'm going for Todoroki.
Tokoyami, Ochako...
Ochako! It's okay, it's okay.
I like you. You're cool. I like you.
I like you, Ochako-chan.
Is this Axta, too? This is the 5th version of Axta.
This is the fifth version. I'm in A, and this is C.
I put this one in here because I'm going for Tokoyachan.
Who's your chance?
What? Marfa and Pyro? Is that possible?
What?
Smile space.
Piran.
Uh, what?
Wait a minute.
Is that possible?
Tokoyami-un
I like him because he's cool.
Is that possible?
That's amazing.
Next.
Yukoriko's petit fluffy Neigurumi.
I'm going for the coffee shop Takina.
What is it?
I want it the most! I want number one.
Can you stay?
All right. - All right.
Let's go.
Ready?
clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap!
Ah! Mizuki?
You're not alone.
But it's a coffee shop.
No, it's not a coffee shop.
I'm Mizuki from the cafe.
Oh, no, I'm stuck.
I've got a bit of Gromi's hair.
Gromi's frizzy hair.
Gromi's frizzy hair! Gromi's frizzy hair!
He's got a frizzy hair!
It's lucky.
Now, here we go, comedy style.
I have the most pieces.
Okay, I'll go first.
I'll take one.
Takina, of course.
Takina is good.
It's a pental type.
Takina, takina, takina.
Takina
The one I wanted.
This is so good!This is a very nice one.
Thank you very much
Takina
I bought 3 of them.
Random real fun!
I wonder if you will do the next festival
Seino
Which one?
Oh, it looks like him.
A little bit.
The one that's lying down.
I think it's the same type.
It's too cute.
He's so cute.
I'll go for the second one.
Takina takina
Seino
That's it!
Oh, I did it.
Oh, it's so cute!
I love this one!
Super cute!
Does that mean she's coming last?
I think it's coming.
I can't wait to see it.
Takina, right?
Here we go.
Let's go!
Takina takina
Takinakinakinakinakinakinakinakinakinakinakinakinakinakinakinakinakinakinakinakinakinakinakinaki.rapeseed
We have it.
When you pull it out at the end...
I knew it!
Yay!
I wanted Takina the most.
Oh, man... this lineup...
It's so hot!
Thank you very much for watching today.
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
Oh, what? Oh, yeah, actually, I was just, uh...
You bought it? Yes, I have.
I need to get your house in order.
Oh, my God.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear Mikuni
Thank you very much!
It's Mikumi's 20th birthday today!
Thank you so much!
I'll enjoy it later.
What are your hopes for the future?
I see...
I've been a junior member of the group for three terms. I've been a junior member of the group for a long time, and I've been working with the 3rd term students.
I want to become stronger both mentally and physically so that I can be in a position to lead the group as the fourth term students join the group.
My goal is to become stronger both mentally and physically at the age of 20.
I also want to take a lot of pictures with the members and go on outings with them.
Let's do it!
These are my goals.
Congratulations!